Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Records SC0756
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Exhibits Department Records, 1969-2010; Accession ARCH_2010_056; 32 Linear Feet; (22 boxes)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Steinbeck in 40s Hollywood (2000) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Steinbeck Notes (2000) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Steinbeck: Research -- Tahoe Apprenticeship (2000) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Steinbeck: Sample Case Titles (2000) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Steinbeck: Texts and Citations, File Copy (2000) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Steinbeck: Titles/Color Trials (2000) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Steinbeck: Wells Fargo Night (2000) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Steinbeck: Yousuf Karsh Obit. 7/14/2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - No Guts, No Glory: A History of the Stanford Alpine Club with Mountaineering Photography (May-August 2000) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - SAC: Alpine Club Book Proposal (2000) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SAC: Case Maps (2000) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - SAC: Citations and Captions Editing/Working Copies (2000) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - SAC: Citations and Captions, Clean File Copy (2000) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - SAC: Custom Color Enlargements and Hardware (2000) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - SAC: Exhibit and Film Festival Flier Sent to ASUL Membership (2000) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - SAC: Expenses/Receipts (2000) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - SAC: Graphics for Window Reveals (2000) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SAC: Installation requirements and Correspondence Re: Exhibits Program (2000) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - SAC: Kinko's Large-Format Posters, Instructions (2000) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SAC: Kinko's Oversize Digital Prints (200) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - SAC: Kudos (2000) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - SAC: Master Layout (2000) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - SAC: Photo Enlargements Info and Notes (2000) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - SAC: Publicity (2000) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - SAC: Sign (2000) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - SAC: Sign -- Jamie's Colortest (2000) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - SAC: To Do (2000) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - SAC: Wall-Mounted Photographs (2000) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - In Company: Robert Creeley's Collaborations (September 2000-January 2001) Case Maps and Layout Lists (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Creeley: Checklists (2000) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Creeley: Colors (2000) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Creeley: Comments Book -- photocopy (2000) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Creeley: Contract and Shipping Paperwork (2000) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Creeley: Correspondence (2000) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Creeley: Crate List (2000) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Creeley: Exhibit Catalog (2000) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Creeley: Insurance and Crate Lists (2000) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Creeley: Large Graphics (2000) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Creeley: Layout Drafts (2000) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Creeley: NYPL #1 (2000) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Creeley: NYPL #2 (2000) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Creeley: New York Public Library Inventory and Storage Chart (2000) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Creeley: Postcard (2000) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Creeley: Postcard Distribution (2000) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Creeley: Press Release Distribution (2000) (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Creeley: Press Release and Distribution List (2000) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Creeley: Publicity -- Newspaper articles, incl. photocopies and originals (2000) (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Creeley: Receipts and Expenses (2000) (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Creeley: Reception Invitation (2000) (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Creeley: Sample Texts and Item Labels (2000) (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Creeley: Sign (2000) (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Creeley: Skylight collage (2000) (not implemented) (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Creeley: Texts and File Copies (2000) (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Creeley: Texts and Quotes / Drafts (2000) (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Points on the Winters Circle: On the Centenary of Poet Yvor Winters (November 2000-February 2001) (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Winters: Booklet (not pursued) (2000) (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Winters: Broadside -- Misc Correspondence (2000) (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Winters: Broadside/Sales (2000) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Winters: Label for Film (2000) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Winters: Permission Requests (2000) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Winters: Lewis Photos/Guide (2000) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Winters: Photos from Dan Winters (2000) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Correspondence/Notes (2000) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Expenses (2000) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Fields Essay (2000) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Galley Proofs, Setting Copy and Final Case Proofs (2000) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Illustration for Broadside (not used) (2000) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Mockup (2000) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Sales and Distribution (2000) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Samples/Ink and Paper (2000) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Specs (2000) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Type Specs of setting copy (2000) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Winters: Portfolio -- Urban Digital Color/Iris Prints (2000) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Winters: "Making the Portfolio" Exhibit (2000) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Winters: Exhibit and Keepsake Publicity (2000) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Winters: Making the Portfolio Photos (2000) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Winters: M and H Type Samples (2000) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Winters: The Strength of Art (2000) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Winters: Symposium (2000) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Winters: Text and Cits. (2000) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Winters: "Two Poets: A Life Together" (2000) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Gilbert White and The Natural History of Selborne: the Bicentennial Exhibit Revisited (February 4-April 8, 2001) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - White Revisited: Retrospective Exhibit (2001) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - White Revisited: Case 1 Exhibit title (2001) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - White Revisited: Case 18 backdrop image (2001) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - White Revisited: Case Texts (2001) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - White Revisited: Catalog (2001) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - White Revisited: Correspondence (2001) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - White Revisited: Laser print dpi tests (2001) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - White Revisited: Maps (2001) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - White Revisited: Paging and Loans (2001) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - White Revisited: Postcard (2001) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - White Revisited: Poster Quote and Type Specs (2001) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - White Revisited: Publicity (2001) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - White Revisited: Receipts and Expenses (2001) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - White Revisited: Sign Design (2001) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Between Two Worlds: S. Ansky at the Turn of the Century (March 15-April 4, 2001) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Ansky: Postcard (2001) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - The Great Art of Knowing: The Baroque Encyclopedia of Athanasius Kircher (April 22-July 22, 2001) -- Book props and board dimensions (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Kircher: Budget and Receipts (2001) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Kircher: Caseback Graphics (2001) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Kircher: Casemaps and Prepsheets (2001) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Kircher: Catalog (2001) (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Kircher: Checklist (2001) (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Kircher: Clock/specs (2001) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Kircher: Color (2001) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Kircher: Fast Signs Specs (2001) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Kircher: Invitation (2001) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Kircher: Lettering for Kircher Magnetic Clock (2001) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Kircher: Mailing and other Publicity Efforts (2001) (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Kircher: Meeting March 29, 2001 (2001) (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Kircher: Notes (2001) (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Kircher: Photoshoot List (2001) (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Kircher: Postcard (2001) (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Kircher: Press Contacts (2001) (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Kircher: Prints and Scans (2001) (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Kircher: Production Schedule (2001) (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Kircher: Proposal to Directors' Office (2001) (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Kircher: Publicity (2001) (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Kircher: Publicity (2001) (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Kircher: Publicity/Distribution of Announcement (2001) (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Kircher: RCA Logo Story (2001) (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Kircher: Repro. Illustrations (2001) (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Kircher: Reveal Panels (2001) (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Kircher: Rotunda Banner (2001) (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Kircher: Rotunda Images (2001) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Kircher: Sign (2001) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Kircher: Slides Scanned for Ella Mazel (2001) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Kircher: Specs/Estimate (2001) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kircher: Specs for Estimate (2001) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kircher: Stanford Magazine article, Fall 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Kircher: Symposium (2001) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Kircher: Texts/File Copy (2001) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Kircher: Water Clock (2001) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Matt Phillips: The Magic in His Prints (August 5 -- November 15, 2001) -- 10Casebacks and Reveal Graphics (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Phillips: Callslips (2001) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Phillips: Casemaps and Prepsheets (2001) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Phillips: Catalogue (2001) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Phillips: Keepsake (2001) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Phillips: Postcard (2001) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Phillips: Postcer Requests (2001) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Phillips: Sketchbook Exhibit (2001) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Partners in Design (Dec. 2, 2001-March 31, 2002) Banners (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Buckminster Fuller Institute Info (2001) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Casemaps and Checklist (2001) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Complete Set of Casemaps (2001) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Dymaxion Map -- Photocopy for Assembly (2001) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Exhibit Binder part 1 (2001) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Exhibit Binder part 2 (2001) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Exhibit Followup (2001) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Label Text Provided by Russell Flinchum (2001) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Labels with Editing Notes (2001) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Labels (Stanford Version) (2001) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Layout -- Peterson Gallery (2001) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Mailing (2001) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Mounting of Solway Prints (2001) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Notes and Materials from Milton Academy (2001) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Notes -- recasting of exhibit text (2001) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Poster/announcement (2001) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Props, Boards, and Hardware (2001) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Publicity (2001) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Shipping Arrangements (2001) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Slides (2001) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Fuller|Sadao: Vitrine for Wichita House Model (2001) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Johannes Lebek: The Artist as a Witness of His Time (Apr. 15-Jul. 6, 2002) Abby Chen on Johannes Lebek (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Lebek: Abby Chen Article re: Johannes Lebek (2002) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Lebek: Announcement/Prospectus (2002) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Lebek: Books Paged from SUL Spec. Coll. (2002) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Lebek: Captions (2002) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Display (2002) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Distribution (2002) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Original Specs for Estimate (2002) (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Estimate and Specs round 2 (2002) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Lebek: Catalogue For Sale Sign (2002) (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Intro/Edited Versions (2002) (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Leab Award and Other Kudos (2002) (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Original Type Search (2002) (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Page Proofs (2002) (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Presscheck (2002) (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Production Files (2002) (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Publicity (2002) (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Scanned Images w/ Editing Notes (2002) (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Typeface Trials (2002) (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Lebek: Catalogue Woodcut Series (2002) (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Lebek: Checklist (2002) (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Lebek: Checklist Editing copy (2002) (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Lebek: Christian Wegner's Photographs (2002) (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Lebek: Correspondence (2002) (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Lebek: Critique first round ‘98 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Lebek: Critique 12/99 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lebek: Exhibit Sign (2002) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lebek: Feb. 2000 Response from Wegner (2002) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lebek: Fran Wegner's Case Maps (2002) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lebek: Fund. Proposal for Lebek Opening (2002) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lebek: Guestbook (2002) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lebek: June ‘99 Proposal and Jan. 2000 Response (2002) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lebek: Layout List (2002) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lebek: Loans and Shipping (2002) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lebek: Mailing (2002) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lebek: Map Revisions and Lists (2002) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lebek: Mockup Critiques (2002) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lebek: Original Proposal and Checklists (2002) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lebek: Other Lebek Exhibits (2002) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Lebek: Other Woodcut Artists (2002) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Lebek: Portfolio (2002) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lebek: Repros (2002) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lebek: Salter Edits w/ Edits (2002) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lebek: Salter Manuscript (2002) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Lebek: Ship List (2002) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Lebek: Ship Lists Annotated by BF (2002) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Lebek: Test Files (2002) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Lebek: Round 2 Test Files (2002) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Making Books in the Woods: The Yolla Bolly Press (July 15-October 13, 2002) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Announcement (2002) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Appellation magazine, vol. 5 no. 1, Feb/March 1997 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Banners (2002) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Bark Magazine, No. 12, Summer 2000 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Case Maps/Annotated Item Lists (2002) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Apprentice Surveys (2002) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Display Notebook 1 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Display Notebook 2 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Early Planning Notes (2002) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Exhibit at Occidental College (2002) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Guestbook and Communication (2002) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: James Robertson Remembered (2002 -- 2 COPIES) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: JR and CR Writings (2002) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Labels (2002) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Large Print Captions of Gallery Guide (2002) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Loan and Insurance Info (2002) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Mailing List (2002) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Mailing List 2002 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Notebook Texts (2002) (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Oral History Proposal (2002) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Ornaments (2002) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Party Mailing (2002) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Press Packets/2nd Wave Publicity (2002) (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Print Magazine May/June 2000 (2002) (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Publicity (2002) (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Publicity (2002) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Publicity Images (2002) (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Questions for interview w/ CR re YB Press (2002) (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Release (2002) (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Repros of Wood Type (2002) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Selections from Apprentice Log (2002) (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Sign (2002) (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Storytellers Series Poster: Labels for Exhibit (2002) (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Susan Sanford Interview (2002) (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: To-Do Lists (2002) (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Yolla Bolly Press: Travelling Exhibition Labels (2002) (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Music in the Stanford University Library Collections: Music Exhibit (2002) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Music Exhibit (2002) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - José Guadalupe Posada and the Taller de Gráfica Popular: Mexican Popular Prints (Nov. 1, 2002-March 15, 2003) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Posada: Banner Images (2003) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Posada: Callslip Buffs (2003) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Posada: Casemaps (2003) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Posada: Catalog/Sales Display (2003) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Posada: Facsimiles (2003) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Posada: Graphics and Text Style Sheet Samples (2003) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Posada: Guest Book (2003) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Posada: Keepsake Display Copy (2003) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Posada: Large Print Exhibit Capts. (2003) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Posada: Postcard (2003) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Posada: Postcard Announcement (2003) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Posada: Poster Requests (2003) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Posada: Prints (2003) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Posada: Sample Mounted Texts (2003) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Posada: Sign (2003) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Posada: Type Trials (2003) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Early to Modern: New Acquisitions in Special Collections and the Stanford University Archives (April 1 -- July 15, 2003) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Early to Modern: Recent Acquisition Banners (2003) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Early to Modern: Biennial Report image scans, Jan. ‘03 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Early to Modern: Case-by-case listing and file copy of labels (2003) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Early to Modern: Case 1 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Early to Modern: Case 2 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Early to Modern: Case 3 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Early to Modern: Case 4 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Early to Modern: Case 5 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Early to Modern: Case 6 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Early to Modern: Case 7 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Early to Modern: Case 8 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Early to Modern: Case 9 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Early to Modern: Case 10 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Early to Modern: Case 11 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Early to Modern: Case 12 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Early to Modern: Case 13 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Early to Modern: Case 14 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Early to Modern: Case 15 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Early to Modern: Case 16 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Early to Modern: Case 17 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Early to Modern: Case 18 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Early to Modern: Case 19 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Early to Modern: Case 20 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Early to Modern: Case 21 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Early to Modern: Case 22 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Early to Modern: Case 23 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Early to Modern: Case 24 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Early to Modern: Exhibit Catalog (2003) (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Early to Modern: Large print captions (moved from binder) (2003) (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Early to Modern: Socrates printouts of books (2003) (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - In Folio: Rare Volumes in the Stanford University Libraries (initial run August 4 November 9, 2003. Modified version installed Feb 18-20, 2005 at Concourse Pavilion, San Francisco) (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Folio: Book Prep Sheets (2003) (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Folio: Book Fair Banners (2003) (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Folio: Book Fair Case Measurements (2003) (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Folio: Book Fair Concourse Floorplans (2003) (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Folio: Book Fair Installation (2003) (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Folio: Book Fair Table Coverings (2003) (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Folio: Book Fair Correspondence (2003) (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Folio: Catalogue (2003) (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- Blueline sent to Friesens (2003) (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- cover (2003) (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- sent to Friesens (2003) (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- Flier (2003) (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- Friesens (2003) (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- pp37-38 reprint (2003) (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- proofs (2003) (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- slipsheet (2003) (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Folio: Catalogue -- TIFFS (2003) (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Folio: Captions, in alphabetical order (2003) (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Folio: Cases 13, 18 (2003) (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Folio: Colors (2003) (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Folio: Custom Cradles (2003) (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Folio: Keepsake (2003) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Folio: Layout (2003) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Folio: Permission (2003) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Folio: Postcard announcement (2003) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Folio: Publicity (2003) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Folio: Requests for posters and banners (2003) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Folio: Scans (2003) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Folio: Scans and Images (2003) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Folio: Winslow Associates (2003) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Felipe Ehrenberg: A Neologist's Art and Archive (November 19, 2003 -- March 15, 2003) Case maps and call slip copies (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Ehrenberg: case titles (2003) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog - BTW TIFFS of Exhibit (2003) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog - copy of files given to Watermark Press 10/09/03 (2003) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog -- Correspondence (2003) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog -- Cover (2003) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog -- Design (2003) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog -- File Copies (2003) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ehrenberg: Catalog -- Specs and Estimates (2003) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Ehrenberg: Colors (2003) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Ehrenberg: Comments book and exhibit catalog display (2003) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Ehrenberg: Corrected Stone Sans Fonts (2003) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Ehrenberg: Facsimiles (2003) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Ehrenberg: Postcard (2003) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ehrenberg: Production (2003) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Ehrenberg: Sign (2003) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - The Rediscovery of Africa, 1400-1900: Antique Maps and Rare Images (April 1 -- August 1, 2004) Announcement (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - African Maps: Banners (2004) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - African Maps: Backdrops 13, 18, 19, 20 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - African Maps: Backdrops/Texts for 19, 20, 13, 18 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - African Maps: Case List (2004) (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - African Maps: Case Maps except 13, 18, 19, 20 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - African Maps: Catalogue (2004) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - African Maps: Catalogue Proof (2004) (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - African Maps: Color Tests (2004) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - African Maps: Delay? (2004) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - African Maps: Facsimile for Exhibit (2004) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - African Maps: Guestbook (2004) (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - African Maps: Invitation and map (2004) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - African Maps: Layout (2004) (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - African Maps: List of Selections (2004) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - African Maps: Poster (2004) (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - African Maps: Production Schedule (2004) (Box 13, Folder 42)